Marriage is good because of sexual
fulfillment. How about if my partner is
not fulfilling my sexual need?
Throughout these months we have been
discussing marriage, singleness, and
self-control. And I don't take it for
granted. It's a privilege for me to
bring us the word of God this morning.
And I'd like to title this short
exhortation, Marriage is good, part two.
Marriage is good, part two.
Can we read our text together from the
book of 1 Corinthians chapter 7 verse 1
and 2, the New Living Translation.
Now, regarding the questions you asked
in your letter,
yes, it is good to abstain from sexual
relations.
But because there is so much sexual
immorality,
each man should have his own wife, and
each woman should have her own husband.
Hallelujah.
There was this story that something
happened some years back.
A man and his wife, they were not
talking.
They had an argument and were not
speaking to each other.
So, the man didn't want to say, "Sorry."
because of his ego.
He didn't want to acknowledge that he
was wrong. And he remembered that, oh,
he has
uh an important meeting. He had to be
somewhere uh the following day, and he
needed to wake up early.
As 5:00 a.m. So,
he didn't want to talk to the wife, so
he wrote a note,
"Wake me up at 5:00 a.m."
And he left it by the bedside for the
wife to read.
And the man slept peacefully.
He woke up the following morning. Guess
what time he woke up?
He woke up 9:00 a.m.
He had a sound sleep. And he woke up, he
was infuriated. He wanted to charge at
the wife, "Why didn't you wake me up?"
And then he saw another note. The wife
had written,
"Wake up. It's 5:00 a.m."
The woman was a good wife, right?
I know. Women will say that.
She
obeyed the man's instruction.
Whether you have been married for 1
month 1 year or 1 decade,
you will agree with me that it takes
humility to succeed in marriage.
It takes It takes serious humility for
marriage to work effectively.
And humility means that
you submit
to someone.
Humility means
you prefer the other person to yourself.
That is humility.
You know,
forget about all the noise going on
online about marriage, why marriage is
not good,
men are
are scum. You know what? Different
words. Women are these.
Sure, I'll fool you
you know. You hear that over and over,
you know.
Forget about all that.
One thing is certain.
Marriage is good because God created it.
Marriage is good. If you're single here,
I'm putting it to you from the word of
God. Everything God created, everything
God created, is good.
Including marriage.
Over and over, every now and then I get
to talk to people, singles, at times
married people. And recently I spoke to
a lady
who
as at then,
possibly till this morning, she's not
interested in marriage.
And the reason
is that
our father did not treat our mother
well.
Our father will beat the mom over and
over onto the point she as a teenager
she threatened the father that I'm going
to harm you if you don't stop beating my
mom.
And to date she's not interested.
And I have another young man who is not
ready
in marriage because to him
it is hard to find a faithful woman.
Because of
what happened in his extended family,
what happened. So, whatever the noise
might be
there is one truth here, marriage is a
good thing.
I grew up my mom taught me to cook and
as a young person I'll be in the kitchen
but I cannot recall the number of times
I cut myself with the knife in the
kitchen.
The question is
is the knife a bad thing?
The a knife is a good tool when you use
effectively
you make your life easy.
But because I didn't know how to handle
the knife well, it cut me over and over
and until I learn.
So, there are people that are being
married or they are in marriage and
their experiences are not good.
It's not because that the marriage is
not good. Possibly it's because of how
they are handling the marriage.
So, marriage is a good thing because God
created it.
Can you say it with me? Marriage is a
good thing.
And if you are sitting beside your
spouse, can you join can you hold their
hands gently?
It's good to be married to you.
Tell them.
If your spouse is looking at you really
you You repent.
You need to change.
Another reason why marriage is good is
this. Marriage is good because of sexual
fulfillment.
Mhm.
Marriage is good because of sexual
fulfillment.
I read from 1 Corinthians chapter 7
verse 2 and 3 New Living Translation.
Paul speaking there. But because there
is so much sexual immorality,
each man should have his own wife and
each woman should have her own husband.
The husband should fulfill his wife's
sexual needs and the wife should fulfill
her husband's need.
We are all sexual beings.
God created us like that.
He gave us the capacity to enjoy
pleasure. Amen.
And he has given us the platform
to enjoy and to express this in
marriage.
So, as I was going through that text,
where Paul said, "The husband should
fulfill his wife's sexual needs and the
wife should fulfill her husband's need."
The question is,
"How about if
my spouse is not fulfilling my need?
What should I do?"
Because there are people like that.
They are married,
but their sexual needs are not being met
within their marriage. So, what should
that person do? Talk about it.
Call your partner.
This is a crucial conversation that can
affect the life of this relationship.
Discuss it
openly.
And if it's like your spouse is not
listening, go for therapy.
Go for therapy.
Amen.
Some years back there was a lady that
came for counseling and that was the
situation for about almost 2 years when
she came. Her husband was not interested
in touching her. Of course, they have a
child already.
And as she was saying it, that I opened
my mouth. Then, "Madam, how have you
been coping?"
Then, when she explained, I said, "See,
your husband is not ready to listen.
I will suggest take this matter to his
family.
He's not ready to listen to pastor, take
it to his family."
And that's what I said, "As you are
leaving me, call them." And that's what
she did over the weekend. So, when she
got there and she told his parents, they
were Yoruba-speaking people. They said,
"Omo yi, lati jo wa ba mi ni."
I said, "Why are you Why have you kept
quiet?
Why didn't you speak out? 2 years?"
I pray there's any family like that that
will be healing.
I said there are ways to be healing.
In the name of Jesus.
So, marriage is good because of sexual
fulfillment.
Oh, you are
an adult. You are working class, you're
single, you are
your emotions are talking to you.
I mean, you should be married. Here in
this town, we don't we we advise you.
Don't wait until you have hundreds of
million before you marry.
Marry within your means.
Marry within your income.
I've seen some guys. They
They are not earning sophisticated
salaries, but they want to marry
sophisticated lady.
You are deceiving yourself.
That is it.
And some of us, our parents, how did
they marry? They marry inside two rooms.
One room self-contained. You will tell
me that was then.
But there are people that still doing it
today. Look for someone within your
financial range.
This is reason for someone.
You are single in this time. Our
marriage counseling classes are
powerful. They are enriching.
Come. You will learn that people that
have been married for 20, 25, almost 30
years, they will tell you the truth.
Our counseling classes are so beautiful,
are so attractive to the point that we
have gotten two Muslims, people that are
non-Christians.
Their friends got married and they asked
them, "Who taught you?" Ah, "Is in this
and they came."
I have counseled one couple like that. I
know of another marriage counselor that
have counseled Muslims.
To tell you how attractive it and good
our marriage counseling is. So, you are
here, you are single,
and you have someone already. Go and
pick the country from. Amen.
And we tell people cut your coat
according to your clothes, not your
size.
Not your size, not even your style,
according to
your size.
I tell young people, I mean, you get
married. If you put 2 million on the
table, you get married.
If you add another zero to it, 20
million, you get married. If you add 100
million,
there will be people they will package
different things and you will spend that
money.
Any amount on the table in this Lagos,
in this country, they will help you
spend it.
So,
get married. And when you come for the
wedding ceremony in church, our service
is so short.
50 minutes, max 1 hour.
We don't want to bore you with story. We
get you married on time and we send you
off to the moon. Just go.
Just go.
Just go. Praise the Lord.
I pray for someone here as a man receive
courage
to take that step
in the name of Jesus. And I see a lady
here receive open eye.
In the name of Jesus, receive favor
in the name of Jesus.
Marriage is good.
Another reason why marriage is good is
this.
Marriage is good for building stable
families and raising godly children.
Stable families.
In Malachi chapter 2 verse 15, God was
speaking through his prophet. New Living
Translation. And God said,
"Didn't the Lord make you one with your
wife?
In body and spirit, you are his.
And what does he want?
Are we there together?
Godly children from your union. Godly
children from your union. So, guard your
heart and remain loyal to the wife of
your youth.
In our societies nowadays, we see in
leaders the way they deal
with us.
The way they deal with their employees.
I mean, the way they embezzle funds. And
the question some of us ask is, "Who
raised this person?
Which family did they come from?"
And we are enjoying what their family
produced.
We are Are we enjoying? We are suffering
what their family produced.
When the father's head is correct and
the woman's head the mother's head is
correct, then the two of them will raise
children whose heads are correct.
That is the reality.
That is the reality. They will raise
children that will be responsible
citizens that will make our societies
more stable.
Growing up, my parents
taught me the value of not lying.
In primary school, my mom would just
perform random search
unannounced.
Bring your bag.
As she goes through the bag, if she
finds any pencil
that she didn't supply,
you will explain tired.
And upon your explanation, you will get
disciplined. You will. You will.
Sometimes you get disciplined you speak
in tongues.
But now this is they say don't beat.
Yes, oh, great now.
It can tilt or border between child
abuse.
So, what do you do? You can deny the
child some rights.
And could be as painful as you applying
physical force or beating them.
Corporal punishment. So, we don't
support that cuz sometimes parents they
do it to to the extreme.
They do it in anger and the child
doesn't get the meaning.
What the child sees anger and abuse and
can leave the child with trauma.
So,
we must raise godly children. Because
the the question we need to ask
ourselves is is this. In that marriage,
what is God really getting?
The hunger together is you and your
spouse, right?
The sexual pleasure is you and your
spouse. The promotion is you and your
spouse, right?
But the seed, these children from it,
that's what God is after.
Godly children. The story of Daniel in
the book of Daniel chapter 1 there about
always fascinates me.
Himself and his
other three Hebrew boys, they were taken
captive
into Babylon. They were taken captive
and that they were preteen or they were
teenagers. Cuz they were young people.
And they brought them into that nation
and they taught them the language of
that nation, the values of that nation
nation, the principle and the philosophy
of that of that nation. But despite all
the
programming that nation did on them,
when it came to food, they said they're
not going to touch something.
Because the roots were there, the
foundation.
They were godly before they left their
country.
And later on, when Daniel interpreted
the dream for Nebuchadnezzar, when he
interpreted that dream, when this Daniel
will give credit, he said, "I thank the
God of my ancestors."
He had left home since. Sometimes as a
parent, the question you ask yourself is
this, can you release your child to
another culture
and you not be there?
Can you?
As a parent, I ask myself this question
over and over.
Can I release my child to another
culture? Because that is what God is
after, godly children that he can be
proud of. My prayer is God will raise
these children through you.
He will raise godly children that will
be upright, that will influence our
culture for him in the name of Jesus. He
will raise them through you.
In Jesus' name.
So, why is marriage good? Another
reason.
Marriage is good because of
companionship and synergy.
It's good because of companionship
and synergy. Let's read from
Ecclesiastes chapter 4 verse 9.
New Living Translation.
Two people are better off than one, for
they can help each other succeed. The
man helps the woman to succeed, The
woman helps the man to succeed. Synergy.
Meaning that you bring our forces
together. The man earns 50,000. The
woman earns 40,000. Together we have
90,000. We can do something substantial
as a team.
And I will say it's not good to do life
alone.
It's not good to do life alone. Life is
challenging.
Life is tough.
That's the way life is anyway. Jesus
said it. In this life you have
tribulation.
Tribulation. So when the time comes,
when life throws challenges at you, how
are you coping? Who is beside you?
Who is beside you?
My prayer is God will give you the right
person.
The right person that will do this
journey with you.
In the name of Jesus. And for those that
are married, God will strengthen your
hands.
Together God will strengthen your union
in the name of Jesus.
Why is marriage good?
Marriage is good because it gives
opportunity to demonstrate Christ's
love.
It gives you opportunity
to demonstrate Christ's love. Let's read
from Ephesians chapter 5 verse 28 and
29.
New Living Translation.
In the same way, husbands ought to love
their wives as they love their own
bodies.
For a man who loves his wife actually
shows love for himself.
No one hates his own body, but feeds and
cares for it, just as Christ cares for
the body.
That is it.
Christ's love is sacrificial.
Christ's love is selfless.
Christ's love is
on is enduring.
So,
in marriage, you are able to to show
this. Scripture says the love of God has
been poured into our hearts by the Holy
Spirit. So, in marriage, you are able to
express this to other people. You know,
as a man,
when you love your wife, you listen to
your wife.
When you love your wife, you care for
her.
When you love your wife, you protect
your wife.
When you love your wife, you are there
for her.
And in the same way,
as a woman, when you love your husband,
you are there for your husband.
You support him.
I mean, see, some some some of us,
the capacity for love that God has given
us,
if I have to measure it in terabytes,
it's much.
We We We That's our design.
And marriage is a good place to express
it. And see,
the love of Christ doesn't say that you
not be hurt.
You will be hurt.
And when you are hurt, what do you do?
You forgive.
Hello, you forgive.
But that's something about marriage, you
always
as you are maturing on your journey, you
will always offend each other.
A time you come when it's like, okay,
now you really understand him, he really
understands you, and the offenses might
reduce, but offenses will not disappear.
They don't disappear because you are
still in the flesh. We are still human.
So, marriage gives us that opportunity
to demonstrate Christ's love.
Marriage is very good until the devil
appeared
in Genesis chapter chapter 3.
It was awesome. It was beautiful. And I
pray for someone in this service,
may your marriage be heaven on earth for
you. Amen.
I say it again, may your marriage be
heaven for you.
On earth in the name of Jesus.
May the Lord pour his beauty over your
family.
In the name of Jesus. So, the devil
appeared
to the marriage of Adam and Eve.
And that tells us that today the devil
is still appearing in marriages.
There is no marriage that is immune
against the devil's attack.
Whether you have been married for just a
month, a year, or 3 year, or 20 year, or
30, the devil is always because the
Bible tells us whatever is born of God
overcomes.
Especially if you and your partner you
are advancing the kingdom of God.
You are pursuing righteousness. You are
saying, "Lord, let your kingdom come.
Let your will be done on earth as it is
in heaven." The devil will be attracted.
So, the devil will show up
in your marriage. And if you're single,
this is it for you. You need to know God
for yourself before you are married.
You need to know how to undo the devil's
tactics.
You need to know how to to take your
authority against the devil because he
will show up.
And I also pray this time around for any
person, any single person here that it
is the devil causing your delay. Satan,
I rebuke you.
Satan, I rebuke you.
Over this son,
over this daughter of God. In the name
of Jesus, every delay is shattered.
In the name of Jesus.
Paul speaking to the Ephesians
Christians in Ephesians chapter 6 verse
10.
I read from the New King James version.
10 and 11. Finally, my brethren, be
strong in the Lord and the the of his
might.
Put on the whole armor of God that you
may be able to stand against the wiles
of the devil.
Every while of the devil against your
family is crushed.
In the name of Jesus. Every tongue
against your family we judge this
morning.
I will condemn in Jesus name.
So, how do we solve the devil's problem
in marriage? How?
The first thing is be free from the same
nature.
Be free.
All of us we have the original sin
nature in us. All of us. The Adamic
nature.
But, you have to be free. And you get
freedom when you come to Christ.
When you come to Christ, God gives you a
new heart. He gives you a new heart.
Paul speaking in 2 Corinthians chapter 5
verse 17,
it says,
"This means that anyone who belongs to
Christ has become a new person. The old
life is gone. A new life has begun."
That is the starting point.
All of us we had different programmings
before we came to Christ.
And that programming cannot succeed. In
fact, that programming is in alignment
with the devil's agenda. So, as long as
you are playing that programming, you
will always have the devil's kind of
results. So, for you to counter the
devil's result, you change. You make
sure you have
that new life in you comes out.
And that new that new life is in Christ.
You You walk with the Holy Spirit to the
point that you are no longer a slave to
sin.
You are no longer a slave to the dictate
of your flesh.
Paul speaking in Romans chapter 4 verse
14,
new living translation,
he says, Romans 6:14,
"Sin is no longer your master, for you
no longer live under the requirements of
the law. Instead, you live under the
freedom of God's grace. Hallelujah."
So, when you come to Christ, you live
under the freedom of God's grace.
The grace of God covers you and you
enjoy
total and true freedom.
Another way to deal with the devils,
problem in marriages, to be full of the
word of God.
Read the Bible for yourself.
Study the Bible for yourself. You don't
understand it, pick another translation
that speaks to you in
simple English language. Study the Bible
for yourself. David, speaking in Psalms
119:11,
David, he said,
"I have hidden your word in my heart
that I might not sin against you."
Another translation says, "I've hidden
your word in my heart so I will not go
bankrupt against you." And David is
saying, "I've hidden my your word in my
heart." And despite eating or hiding the
word of God in his heart, he still did
some sins.
How about if he didn't even put any
word?
Can you imagine? So, that David David is
a man like us, he has emotions like us.
So, the the secret is in you filling
your heart with the enough of the word
of God.
So, when the devil comes, the word will
come out.
Feed your life with the word of God.
Paul encouraging the Colossians in
Colossians 3:16,
New Living Translation. He said to them,
he said, "Let the message about Christ
in all its richness fill your lives.
Teach and counsel each other with all
the wisdom it gives. Sing psalms and
hymns and spiritual songs to God with
thankful hearts. Read the Bible. Listen
to the word. Now, nearly everybody has
Bible apps. As you're going about your
business, you don't have time to read,
listen. Listen to the As you're
listening, it's entering your spirit.
It's entering. And you may not be able
to quote the Bible verbatim, but you can
paraphrase it, right? When you know,
when you have heard it over and over, it
becomes part of your language.
Fill the word
of God. Fill the word of God into your
hearts.
Another way to deal with the devil's
problem in marriage is this: submit
fully to the Holy Spirit.
Learn to submit to the Holy Spirit.
Without the Holy Spirit's involvement in
our lives, we will self-destruct.
Without the Holy Spirit helping a
believer, a believer cannot even live
the Christian life
without the Holy Spirit. So, submit
fully to his leadership. Submit fully to
his authority.
Submit to him. Let's read together from
Galatians chapter 5, verse 16
and 17.
Galatians 5:16. [music]
So, I say, "Let the Holy Spirit guide
your lives.
Then you won't be doing what your sinful
nature craves.
The sinful nature wants to do evil,
which is just the opposite of what the
spirit wants.
And the spirit gives us desires that are
the opposite of what the sinful nature
desires.
These two forces are constantly fighting
each other. So, you are not free to
carry out your good intention. I pray
for someone that might be having that
struggle. the Holy Spirit grants you
victory.
In the name of Jesus.
Let's continue in verse 22. Verse 22.
But the Holy Spirit produces this kind
of fruits in our lives. Can we read them
together? Love,
joy, peace, [music]
patience, kindness, goodness,
faithfulness, gentleness, and
self-control.
These There is no law against these
things. Hallelujah. Who produces these
fruits in our lives? The Holy Spirit.
The Holy Spirit.
You and your partner, you're having a
conversation and it's getting hot. Your
partner is blowing hot. That is not when
you should blow hot.
You to the Holy Spirit. The Holy Spirit
will give you that word that you can
speak [music] that will soften the
situation, will calm your partner's
heart. And later on, you may bring your
points. You may bring your points.
Learn to listen to the Holy Spirit.
Because he knows our emotions and he
knows how he can resolve whatever
matter. Years back,
my son and my wife had this
misunderstanding.
In the morning, it started the previous
night. In the morning, it continued.
Now, I'm going to work.
I wasn't talking to her. She wasn't
talking to me.
Drive from home to work.
I increased the volume of the car radio.
Cuz I didn't want to hear anything.
I was playing music just to doubt that
noise.
And then I got to work.
Then I thought of what can I do to teach
[music] this young girl a lesson?
You know, that she shouldn't repeat
that. And I was getting ideas, you know,
oh, I'll do this. I'll do this.
In fact, one of them, if I had carried
it out, my in-laws would have heard
about me.
So, I had those things I was to do.
And then this idea [music] came.
Buy her a new phone. Oh.
I discarded that one. That's no This one
will not achieve the objective.
Then about 45 minutes after it came
again.
I pushed it down. Then again, this time
around.
Of course, I don't I immediately forgot
me.
And then I checked my account balance. I
could afford a new phone. So, I got this
new phone. Before that event, our phone
charger was bad. So, I I knew she needed
a new [music] phone. So, I got her a new
phone. And then when I got home, she got
home before me. She opened the door for
me and
and welcome, welcome.
You know.
So, I dropped the pack of the phone on
the table. And then I I walked away. I
said, "That's your phone." I just walked
to the bedroom to change. And then from
nowhere, a mighty torrent of force from
behind. She grabbed me. She said, "I'm
sorry."
>> [applause]
>> And then I also said, "I'm sorry."
And then the chain
just like that.
Only just a phone.
And everything
Listen.
Is the Is It may sound simple because
for me it was too simple to be the
solution.
It was too simple.
The question I asked myself, "How about
if I didn't listen to the Holy Spirit?"
How about if I'd done the other things I
wanted to do?
I wouldn't know the trajectory of the
marriage.
So, the [music]
lesson for us here is let's submit to
the Holy Spirit. And sometimes when the
Holy Spirit is giving us instructions,
that instruction might sound stupid or
foolish.
It will not be rational.
How can someone offend you?
Someone is at fault and the solution is
you give a gift.
The logic mind says, "Deal with it,
right?"
But that wasn't the solution.
>> [music]
>> As couples, let's learn to listen to
reason it because it's always there.
It's always there. It's always there.
The last point on how to deal with the
devil's problem in marriage is this:
Exercise your authority in Christ.
Jesus speaking in Matthew chapter 18
verse 18 to 19 New Living Translation,
Jesus said, "I tell you the truth.
Whatever you forbid on earth [music]
will be forbidden in heaven.
And whatever you permit on earth will be
permitted in heaven." Verse 19, "I also
tell you this, if two of you
agree here on earth concerning anything
you ask, my Father in heaven will do it
[music] for you. Hallelujah."
As husband and wife, know that you have
the authority to rebuke the devil in
your family affairs.
Exercise that authority.
Exercise it. As the man, you are the
head of that family. You have spiritual
authority over your family. Pray for
your wife.
In Genesis, Isaac was married to Re-
Rebekah and Rebekah was not conceiving
on time. Scripture said, "And Isaac
prayed for his wife."
>> [music]
>> He exercised his authority over the
wife.
Together, join your hands together and
come against the devil. You know, this
same passage that says, "Whatever if two
of you agree on earth concerning
anything." I read another translation
that paraphrased it. It said, "If what
the two of you are asking for doesn't
exist, God will create it.
God will create it.
So, husband and wife, you have that
power of agreement.
Agree, whatever you agree on earth
will be permitted. Whatever you forbid
on earth will be forbidden in heaven.
Whatever you permit on earth, heaven
will support you.
My prayer is in your home there will be
solutions.
I say in your family there will be
solutions. In the name of Jesus.
I would like to wrap up with this. In
our societies nowadays,
there are so much pressures
against the singles.
Singles, anytime we see them the first
question is, "When are you getting
married? Are you not interested in
marriage? What are you doing?" As if
they don't know.
They do.
So, if you read from 1 Corinthians
chapter 7,
there Paul speaks positively about
singleness.
He said the singles, they don't have
distractions.
They can devote their time, their
attention to the things of God. And God
appreciates that. So, there is honor in
being single.
Our Lord himself was not was not
married. He remained single. John the
Baptist was not married if we purpose.
Paul himself was single throughout the
time was carrying out his ministry. And
what I am reading today
was actually written by single man.
So, let's appreciate the singles.
>> [cheering]
>> Let's appreciate them.
>> [applause]
>> So, when we see them, we should support
them.
They have emotional needs. Let's support
Let's be there for them. Let's advise
them in love.
Don't put any pressure on them.
God will help us. and for our singles,
we love you.
We appreciate you and we honor you.
Praise the Lord.
So, the biblical idea is that singleness
is good.
Marriage is good.
And depending and this depends on the
calling on the man's life. There are
people that God has given the capacity
to be remain single.
>> [music]
>> They are devoted to their extended
family, they are devoted to their job
and they are fine.
And the same way, marriage is good. If
you're now married, you're devoted to
your partner, to your children and to
the will of God for your marriage.
>> [music]
>> Come upper Sunday, we'll continue on
this topic. God bless you in the name of
Jesus.
>> [applause]
>> Please, can we take a moment to pray?
I just want you to pray.
If you're married, can you can you ask
God, continue to guide us. I present my
family to you, Lord. I had to direction,
I had to your instruction in
righteousness. I had that
you will grant us more understanding,
more understanding. Can you pray for
your children in that marriage? You are
trusting God for the fruit of the womb
in that marriage. We pray for
fruitfulness. Can you go out and ask God
under this grace, Lord, we ask you for
fruitfulness. In the name of Jesus. If
you are single, can you ask Lord direct
my paths.
Lord, lead me.
Lord, I ask for miracle of divine
connection this week.
Direct my steps. The steps of the
righteous are ordered by God. Direct my
steps
in the name of Jesus. Let your favor, oh
God, walk for me in the new dimension.
Father, we thank you.
And in the name of Jesus, I speak
against any attack of the devil against
your family.
Satan, I rebuke you.
I pray your marriage will last your
lifetime.
Your marriage shall be peaceful.
Your marriage shall be enduring.
Your marriage shall be established. In
the name of Jesus. We ask for
fruitfulness in that marriage. In the
name of Jesus. We prophesy fruitfulness
in your marriage. In the name of Jesus.
Lord, thank you for promotion coming to
that family. Thank you for lifting their
heads. In the name of Jesus. Thank you
for giving them the way out of that that
problem. In the name of Jesus. And Lord,
thank you for your son that is single.
Thank you for your daughter that is
single. You know, thank you because your
favor is working for them. In the name
of Jesus. Thank you for multiplying
their joy. Thank you, oh God, for
satisfying their mouth with good things.
Thank you for granting their heart
desires. Thank you, Lord, for helping
them to find and to fulfill purpose. In
the name of Jesus. We bless you, Father.
We give you praise.
>> [music]
>> In Jesus' name. Amen. We are still
praying. I just want to take a moment to
pray for that person.
You're here in this service. You're
watching online. You know your
relationship with God is not the best.
You know you have done some things that
God is not proud of you. And you are not
even proud enough to come before God.
But God's hands are ever open. And this
morning God is saying, "Let's make up."
Please, you're that person you want to
say, "Lord, I want to give my life to
you." Can you just put your hand on your
chest?
It's between you and [music] God. God
has a beautiful plan for you. Can you
put your hand on your chest? If your
hand is on your chest, can you raise the
other hand to God? Just raise the other
hand. Thank you, my sister. Thank you.
God bless you. Watching online, please,
this is your moment. Can you just say
that prayer? Can you say this prayer
with me? Say, say,
I come to you today
>> [music]
>> in the name of Jesus. I ask you
for forgiveness of my sins. Today,
>> [music]
>> I receive Jesus Christ as my personal
Lord and Savior. Thank you, Father, for
saving me in Jesus' [music] name. Amen."
Let me pray for you. Father, we bless
you for these people you have drawn to
yourself this morning. We pray that you
write their names in the Lamb's Book of
Life. We pray that you establish them in
your vineyard. And they will take root
and they'll become more like your son.
Thank you, Father, for this grace
>> [music]
>> in Jesus' name. Amen.
Daystar, raising role models.